Put lunchbox
Pick up lunchbox
Open lid
Put lunchbox
Put lid
Open bin
Pick up lunchbox
Empty lunch box
Place lunchbox
Open lid
Pick up lunchbox
Empty lunchbox
Place lunchbox
Pick up rubbish
Put rubbish in bin
Push bin back
Pick up lunchbox
Pick up towel
Clean lunchbox
put kitchen towel in bin
pick up lunch box
place lunch box
pick up sandwiches
put sandwiches in lunch box
put in lunch box
pick up lid
put lid on lunchbox
pick up lunchbox
open fridge
place lunch box
close fridge
open cupboard
grab crisp packet
grab crisp
put crisp packet
close cupboard
open cupboard
grab chocolate
Close cupboard
Put chips in lunch box
Put chocolate in lunch box
Close lunch box
Pick up lunch box
Open fridge
Put lunch box
Close fridge
Pick up bottles
Open bottle
Turn on water
Fill bottle
Close bottle
Shake bottle
Open bottle
Pour out water
Close bottle
Pick up bottle
Open lid
Fill up
Close bottle
Shake bottle
Pour out water
Shake
Open bottle
Pour out bottle
Fill up bottle
close bottle
open fridge
place bottle in fridge
pour swash
put down bottle
fill bottle
close bottle
shake bottle
open bottle
pour bottle
close bottle
place bottle
pick up bottle
fill bottle
turn off tap
pick up lid
close bottle
Test bottle
Open fridge
Put bottle in fridge
Close fridge
Pick up bin bag
Place bin
Put bin bag
Pick up bin
Turn on water
Place bin
Open cupboard
Take cleaning liquid
Pour cleaning liquid
Test water
Fill bin
continue filling bin
pick up sponge
wash bin
continue washing bin
squeeze sponge
pour water out of the bin
wash outside of bin
wipe bin
squeeze sponge
turn on tap
rinse bin
turn off tap
pour bin
pick up towel
wipe bin
continue wiping bin
wipe outside of bin
put bin down
put towel in bin
get bag
open bag
shake bag
put bag in bin
open bag
put lid on bin
push bin back
turn on tap
turn off tap
throw away sponge
open cupboard
take new sponge
place sponge
close cupboard
pick up plate
brush crumbs
put crumbs in bin
wash side
[END SUBTITLE]